The truth is just a trick of light.
Slow Burn is a mystery, crime, drama film directed by Wayne Beach.
A district attorney is involved in a 24-hour showdown with a gang leader and is, at the same time,
being manipulated by an attractive assistant district attorney and a cryptic stranger.
Ford Cole, played by Ray Liotta.
Luther Pinks, played by LL Cool J.
Isaac Duperde, played by Mekhi Phifer.
Nora Timmer, played by Jolene Blalock.
Ty Trippin, played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Jeffrey Sykes, played by Taye Diggs.
Slow Burn is a 2005 American drama thriller film directed by Wayne Beach
and starring Ray Liotta, Jolene Blalock and LL Cool J.
It is notable for the extended period between production and eventual release.
A crime drama, the film was produced in 2003, was finally given a showing at the 2005 Toronto
International Film Festival, and finally got a proper theatrical release in 2007.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.